Finding Aid for University of Michigan. Dept. of Medicine and Surgery Theses, 1851-1878
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Medical Theses
  - Class of 1870
    - Blackburn, Thomas Smith (d. 1877), "Inflammation", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Boardman, Irving Randolph LeRoy (d. 1898), "Hernia", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Boon, George Dallas (d. 1905), "Pneumonia", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Boughton, Darius Fremont (d. 1909), "Mental Therapeutics", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Bowes, William Willmott (d. 1898), "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Brough, Samuel (d. 1907), "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Brown, Herman Erastus, "Diphtheria", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Canedy, Francis Joel, "The Pathology of the Inflammatory Process", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Case, Calvin Almond (d. 1922), "Fractures", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Case, Gideon Seward, "Typho-Malarial Fever", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Case, Marvin Truman, "The Therapeutical Action of Bromide of Potassium", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Coope, Adelbert Franklin (d. 1902), "Epithelial Cell", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Couse, Joseph Peter (d. 1900), "Pneumonia", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Covert, Samuel (d. 1870), "Influence of Sunlight", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Crane, Horatio Nelson (d. 1875), "Inflammation", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Creveling, Joseph P. (d. 1918), "Uterine Moles", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Crooker, George Atherton, "Puerperal Fever", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Doty, Edwin Tyler (d. 1914), "Morbid Blood Changes", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Eccles, Jacob Vandegrift, "Phlogosis", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Ewing, Frank (d. 1906), "Remittent Fever", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Farnum, James Kelley (d. 1911), "Origin of Medicine", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Farrand, John Northrop (d. 1880), "The Circulation of the Blood", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Fox, Asa L., "Alcohol as a Medicine", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Gardner, Ira Kilbourn (d. 1913), "Emansio Mensium", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - George, Franklin (d. 1897), "Indigestion", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Greaves, William (d. 1907), "Hygiene", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Hagadorn, Johnson William (d. 1910), "Inflammation", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Hall, Arthur George (d. 1877), "Cholera Infantum", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Hall, Charles J. (d. 1900), "Hygiene and the Natural Laws", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Hamilton, Alfred James (d. 1917), "Physical Exploration of the Lungs", 1870 (Reel 32)
    - Harding, Horace J. (d. 1910), "The Treatment of Ulcers", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Harper, David (d. 1886), "Light and Air", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Hathaway, William McClure (d. 1888), "Dentition", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Hews, Charles Dean (d. 1909), "Ventilation", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Howland, George Washington Lafayette (d. 1900), "Dyspepsia", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Ikeler, William Miles (d. 1903), "Pneumonia", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Jackson, Gustavus, "Bloodletting", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Jenks, Halsey Barnes (d. 1907), "Acute Articular Rheumatism", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Jewett, Henry Smith, "The Value of a Practical Knowledge of Chemistry to a Physician", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Kinnan, Isaac Newton, "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Lewis, James McAdory (d. 1889), "Diabetes Mellitus", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Lockwood, George Stickney (d. 1909), "The Use and Abuse of Opium", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - McHenry, Thomas Conner (d. 1892), "Inflammation", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - McInnes, Andrew, "Dysentery", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - McKenzie, William Robert (d. 1923), "The Organogens", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Manson, Peter (d. 1914), "Inflammation", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Matheson, Alexander Ross, "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 33)
    - Maxson, William Babcock, "Neuralgia", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Millard, Orson (d. 1917), "Carbolic Acid", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Morrison, William Pass, "Emphysema", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Overfield, Adam (d. 1910), "Glycerina", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Plessner, Robert (d. 1872), "Diphtheria", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Ramey, Wilson (d. 1874), "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Richardson, Elias Smith, "Splenology", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Robertson, Alexander Patrick (d. 1918), "Epidemic Cholera", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Robinson, Robert Emmett, "The Student of Medicine", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Roe, John Orlando (d. 1915), "Abortion", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Rutan, John Allen (d. 1871), "Hygiene", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Seymour, Henry Parker (d. 1885), "Diphtheria", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Shaw, Thomas (d. 1917), "Emotion", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Sheehy, John F. (d. 1887), "A Comparison Between the Mineral and Vegetable Medicines", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Swetnam, James Manoah (d. 1921), "The Agency of Deficient Ventilation in the Production of Disease", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Taylor, Wallace, "Alcohol", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Thompson, Charles Marsh (d. 1902), "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Tidd, Ebenezer J. (d. 1906), "Physiology of Reproduction", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Titus, Charles Foster (d. 1883), "Minutiae of Practice", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Tock, Orson Wilson (d. 1913), "Bright's Disease", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Van Camp, Joshua Emanuel (d. 1904), "Medicine-a Science", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Whaley, Simeon Odell, "Typhoid Fever", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Wight, Alden Hebbard (d. 1913), "Epidemic Dysentery", 1870 (Reel 34)
    - Wilder, Hoyt Romeo (d. 1901), "Hygiene of Children from Birth to the Period of Weaning", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Wilkinson, William Henry (d. 1890), "The Triumph of Electricity", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Williams, Thomas Jefferson (d. 1912), "The Physiology of Menstruation", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Wilson, George Warren (d. 1907), "Fever", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Winslow, Andrew (d. 1905), "The Treatment of Abortion", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Witting, Samuel Nelson (d. 1904), "Typhus Fever", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Work, James Anderson, "The Operation of Trephining", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Wright, Peter Salesberry (d. 1871), "Cynanche Trachealis", 1870 (Reel 35)
    - Yengling, Arthur C., "Auscultation of the Respiratory Organs", 1870 (Reel 35)
  - Class of 1871
    - Abbott, Edwin Kirk (d. 1918), "Typhus and Typhoid", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Adams, Adam, "Digestion", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Amerman, Albert Samuel (d. 1903), "Urea", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Arkley, Alexander Thayer (d. 1908), "Typhoid Fever", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Baker, Smith (d. 1922), "Intermittent Fever", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Barclay, Thomas Stirling (d. 1909), "Hunger, Thirst, and Food", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Barton, Rufus Franklin (d. 1919), "Pneumonia", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Bennett, Charles Tanner (d. 1908), "Scarlatina", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Boyd, Robert Hamilton (d. 1882), "Rheumatism", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Briggs, Wallace Alvin, "Life and Death", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Bukey, James (d. 1885), "Intermittent Fever", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Campbell, Archibald B. (d. 1921), "Typhoid Fever", 1871 (Reel 35)
    - Campbell, Malcolm Munroe, "Alcohol in Health", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Carey, Robert Beatty (d. 1921), "The Phenomena of Sleep", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Carpenter, Thomas Jefferson (d. 1913), "Inguinal Hernia", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Churchill, Frederick C., "The Treatment of Disease", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Clark, Robert Washington (d. 1871), "Functional Diseases of the Stomach", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Cowell, Joseph Harris (d. 1920), "Prolapsus Uteri", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Culver, Elijah, "Opium", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Davis, Albert Lewis (d. 1877), "Pneumonia", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Davis, Cyrus Griswold (d. 1899), "The Circulation of the Blood", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Dills, Spencer (d. 1872), "Insolation", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Dills, Thomas Jefferson (d. 1899), "Erysipelas", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Doane, Luigi Galvani (d. 1909), "The Blood", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Douglass, William Murray, "Cinchona", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Downer, Flavius Josephus (d. 1905), "Hygiene", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Downie, Colin Leitch (d. 1916), "Diphtheria", 1871 (Reel 36)
    - Duncan, James Alexander, "Early History of Medicine", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Engle, Perry, "A Treatise on Some of the Most Common Forms of Hernia, Including Diagnosis and Treatment", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Goodwin, Eugene Augustus (d. 1910), "Digestion", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Gray, Thomas Hamilton (d. 1911), "Digestion", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Greenamyer, John David, "Mind Versus Disease, Their Physical Relations", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Hagadorn, Alexander Dunlap (d. 1918), "Wounds", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Harris, Harvey Alexander (d. 1877), "Animal Nutrition", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Hatch, Theodore Lincoln (d. 1913), "An Investigation of the Physiological Laws that are Essential to a Healthy Nutrition", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Henriques, Edward Cutler (d. 1893), "Typhoid Fever", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Hickey, Amanda (Sanford) (d. 1894), "Eclampsia Puerperalis", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Hill, Hampton Eugene (d. 1894), "Pneumonitis", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Hobart, Marl Estus (d. 1893), "Heart Sounds", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Hunt, David Winslow (d. 1922), "Digestion", 1871 (Reel 37)
    - Johnson, Richard Monroe (d. 1909), "General Peritonitis, its Pathology and Treatment", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Kaiser, Augustus (d. 1894), "Abhandlung uber Venerische Krankheiten", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Kinyon, Benjamin (d. 1911), "The Heart", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Lacy, Charles Silas (d. 1899), "Alcohol", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Leyman, Emery Herschel (d. 1915), "The Human Embryo", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Lovett, Arthur S., "Hysteria", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Lovewell, Charles Hubert (d. 1919), "The Science of Medicine", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - McGeachy, Duncan James (d. 1882), "Some Observations on the Uses and Abuses of Abortion", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - McMichael, Oliver Henry (d. 1916), "Typhoid Fever", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Mennig, Louis, "The Etiology of Fever", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Messenger, Sanford Squires (d. 1890), "Opium", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Mills, Cornelius (d. 1922), "Flooding", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Mills, John Lewis (d. 1905), "Stricture of the Male Urethra", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Morden, Marshal Roblin (d. 1918), "Organic Diseases of the Stomach", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Morgan, Charles Augustus, "Inguinal Hernia", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Muir, Daniel Henry (d. 1923), "Anaesthesia", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Nichols, Devillo John, "Acute Dysentery", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Nicholson, William Addison, "Tetanus", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Post, Samuel Moses (d. 1909), "Delirium Tremens", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Rex, Robert George (d. 1887), "Pathology", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Richardson, William (d. 1923), "The Blood", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Rockwell, John Elias (d. 1876), "Digestion", 1871 (Reel 38)
    - Root, Frank (Franklin) Willoughby (d. 1898), "Transfusion", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Shank, Rush Jesse (d. 1908), "Alcohol", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Sihler, Christian (d. 1919), "Croupous Laryngitis", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Silverwood, William F., on intermittent fever, 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Simons, Manly Hale (d. 1922), "Acute Pneumonia", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Spooner, Jared (d. 1910), "Pseudomembranous Laryngitis", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Sullivan, John Tyler, "Observations on the Works of Hippocrates", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Todd, David Byron (d. 1916), "Hygienic Measures in the Treatment of Fevers", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Turner, James, "Anaesthetics in Surgery and Parturition", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Turner, Robert (d. 1911), "Conjunctivitis", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Tuttle, John Laton (d. 1907), "Inflammation", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Upjohn, Henry Uriah (1843-1887), "Auscultation", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Van Buren, Martin Franklin (d. 1919), "Hernia", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Wellings, Samuel Hyatt (d. 1923), "Remittent Fever", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Whinery, Marshall (d. 1887), "The Pathology of Carcinoma, More Especially on Carcinoma Uteri", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Whitehall, Samuel (d. 1923), "Dysentery", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Williams, Harvey (d. 1909), "Narcotics", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Williams, Martin Leroy, "Scarlet Fever", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Wilson, James Arthur (d. 1891), "Cholera Infantum", 1871 (Reel 39)
    - Wisewell, Francis Henry (d. 1921), "Alcoholism", 1871 (Reel 39)
  - Class of 1872
    - Adams, Albert Wilfred (d. 1922), "Rubeola", 1872 (Reel 39)
    - Anderson, Elsie (Fowler) (d. 1895), "Typhoid Fever", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Ayres, Ann (d. 1876), "Puerperal Fever", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Bacheler, Joseph Howard (d. 1899), "Malaria, Its Source and Effects", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Barney, Elfred Rowe (d. 1915), "Scarlatina", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Boyd, Robert Elbert (d. 1878), "Paralysis", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Boynton, Madison Eugene (d. 1912), "Physical Evidence of Pulmonary Disease", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Burdick, John Fosdick (d. 1886), "The Anatomy and Physiology of the Skin and its Appendages", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Chandler, Samuel Wooster (d. 1903), "Conception", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Chapin, Samuel (d. 1920), "Hernia", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Cook, Henry Humphreville, "Scarlatina", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Daly, Oliver Peter (d. 1891), "Pneumonia", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Ditmars, William Remma (d. 1919), "Synopsis of Scarlatina and its Treatment", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Donelson, Charles Park (d. 1911), "Zymotic Poisons or the Causes of Disease", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Duncanson, Ethelbert Ernest, "Medical Electricity", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Esterly, Francis Powell (d. 1919), "Pneumonia", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Fasquelle, Mark Francis, "Typhoid Fever", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Fisher, Edward Combie, "Progressive Paralysis of the Insane", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Fitzbutler, Henry (d. 1901), "Circulation", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Flick, Otis Clay (d. 1890), "What Constitutes Disease", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Freund, Isidore, "Stricture of the Male Urethra", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Fuller, James Henry, "The Study of Clinical Medicine and Duty of Junior Practitioner", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Galentine, John Jacob (d. 1881), "Scarlatina", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Gibson, Alexander Chambers, "Syphilis", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Green, Joseph (d. 1872), "Spermatorrhoea", 1872 (Reel 40)
    - Harris, Philander Abbey, "Scarlatina", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hartman, Samuel Duff, "Intermittent Fever", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Haskin, Henry Steiner (d. 1919), "Acute Articular Rheumatism", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Henderson, Alvin Charles (d. 1899), "Vaccination", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Herres, Simon (d. 1885), "Cholera", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hewitt, John Emery (d. 1881), "Bilious Fever", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hill, William Ellis (d. 1912), "Phthisis Pulmonalis", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hogan, Patrick Francis (d. 1916), "Venereal Diseases", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Houghton, Loren Alphonzo (d. 1907), "Consumption", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hoyt, Benjamin Rush (d. 1921), "Speculative Pathology", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hull, Henry (d. 1909), "Hygiene and Hygienic Agents", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Hull, Ruth Emma, "Vis Medicatrix Naturae", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Huntington, William Clark, "The Sympathetic Nervous System", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Johnston, Isiah (d. 1880), "Delirium Tremens", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Jones, Franklin B. (d. 1905), "Scarlatina", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Jones, John Robert (d. 1922), "Mental Influence", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Jones, Lafayette (d. 1916), "Diagnosis", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Jump, David William (d. 1913), "A Short Review of the Normal Conditions of the Alimentary Canal and of Some of its Morbid States together with Reflections upon Dyspepsia, its Causes and Treatment", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Kelly, Josiah Raymond (d. 1909), "The Common Causes of Disease", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Kersey, Charles Anselm, "The Anatomy and Action of the Kidney", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Kirkland, Helen Maria (Upjohn) (1839-1901), "Haematics", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Lawless, James Thomas, "Puerperal Convulsions", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - Lundy, Charles J. (d. 1892), "Acute Lobar Pneumonia", 1872 (Reel 41)
    - McCormick, Colin, "Phthisis Pulmonalis", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - McIlvain, John Crayton (d. 1899), "Hints on Diet", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Mahanna, Dennis (d. 1875), "Diacritica Signa", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Marshall, Andrew (d. 1922), "Typhoid Fever", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Meredith, George Alben (d. 1908), "Paludal Miasmatic Poison", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Metcalf, Charles Nathan (d. 1896), "Gonorrhoea", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Miller, Joshua (d. 1901), "Acute Dysentery", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Mitchell, Archibald (d. 1900), "Erysipelas", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Morse, Frederick Langdon (d. 1888), "Digitalis", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - News, Annie (d. 1896), "Puerperal Fever", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Newton, Jasper Pierce, "Cinchona", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Oldfield, Anthony (d. 1905), "Diagnosis", 1872 (Reel 42)
    - Owen, Frank King (d.1905), SEE listing for, 1869 (Reel 42)
    - Palmer, Stephen Elmer (d. 1917), "Digestion", 1869 (Reel 42)
    - Parker, Edgar (d. 1888), "Vis Medicatrix Naturae", 1869 (Reel 42)
    - Pelton, Levant Ora, "Anatomy, Function, and Diseases of the Uterus", 1869 (Reel 42)
    - Phelps, Oscar Samuel (d. 1914), "The Solar Plexus", 1869 (Reel 42)
    - Ranney, Thomas George (d. 1916), "Diathesis", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Reed, Albert Henry (d. 1893), "Anaesthetics and Anaesthesia", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Rice, Watson Emmons, "Chronic Albuminuria", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Romig, Samuel Vincent (d. 1920), "Enteric Fever", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Ryno, Wakeman (d. 1918), "Malarial Fevers", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Searing, Anna Hutchinson (d. 1912), "Indigestion", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Shelton, George Hather, "Remittent Fever, its Cause, Symptoms, and Treatment", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Smith, Bowles Colgate (d. 1883), "Hernia", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Snow, Sparrow A., "Scarlatina", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Sprowl, John Shafer (d. 1916), "Treatment of Disease", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Stevens, George Willard (d. 1906), "Digestion", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Stiles, Milton Dan, "Diphtheria", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Stowell, Charles Henry (1850-1932), "Human Blood", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Taylor, William James (d. 1921), "Circulation of the Blood", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Tennant, Joshua (d. 1899), "Digestion", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Truman, Alexander Smith (d. 1923), "Puerperal Fever", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Van Antwerp, Samuel Carter (d. 1909), "Hygienic Influences", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Warner, Helen Frances (d. 1905), "Endocervicitis", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Weadock, Thomas McMullen (d. 1905), "Hernia", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Willcox, William Richard, "Pneumonitis", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Wise, Julius (d. 1902), "Chancroid, its History and Diagnosis", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Wright, Joel Fitz, "Digestion and Absorption", 1869 (Reel 43)
    - Wright, Peter Wesley (d. 1909), "Life, or Vital Force" [Degree granted in 1873], 1869 (Reel 43)
  - Class of 1873
    - Aitcheson, William (d. 1909), "Circulation", 1873 (Reel 43)
    - Atwood, Oliver Madison (d. 1916), "Diphtheria", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Bailey, Sarah Elizabeth (Brown) (d. 1901), "The Value of the Ophthalmoscope to the General Practitioner", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Banks, Sarah Gertrude (b. 1839), "Insanity, a Sympathetic Accompaniment of Uterine Disease", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Batson, Lafayette (d. 1880), "Digestion", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Bessac, Henry Bertrand (d. 1904), "The Prevention of Disease", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Best, Robert Bruce (d. 188?), "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Bigelow, Charles Sumner, "The Nervous System", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Brown, Isaac Ellsworth (d. 1890), "Cataract", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Brown, John Wing (d. 1914), "Diphtheria, its Pathology and Treatment", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Burdick, William Nelson (d. 1921), "The Circulation of the Blood", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Bushnell, Homer (d. 1909), "Pneumonitis", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Call, Emma Louise, "Arrangement of Neurine in the Cerebro-Spinal Axis", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Campbell, William W. (d. 1902), "Hygiene of Children", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Choate, William Edward (d. 1892), "Dysentery", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Cochran, Clarence Fletcher (d. 1916), "Digestion", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Colladay, Stephen Mershon, "Digestion", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Copp, Josephine Marie (d. 1874), "Chemical Action Relating to Human Physiology and Pathology", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Cotton, William Henry (d. 1875), "Dyspepsia", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Craig, John Calvin (d. 1914), "The Blood", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Culley, John Wesley (d. 1907), "Intermittent Fever", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Davis, John Anderson (d. 1915), "Diphtheria", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Doty, Lambert Le Roy (d. 1917), "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Elmer, Emmet Seward, "Blood", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Evans, Ephraim Beverage (d. 1902), "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Evans, Thomas Robison (d. 1896), "Tobacco", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Foote, Louis Adelbert (d. 1904), "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Fullerton, George Erskine (d. 1900), "The Blood", 1873 (Reel 44)
    - Gandy, Joseph Edward, "Papaver Somniferum", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Gee, James Edward (d. 1908), "Acute Rheumatism", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Grannis, William Reuben (d. 1873), "Pulmonary Tuberculosis", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hall, Arthur Sherman (d. 1876), "Acute Articular Rheumatism", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hall, Edmund Murray, "Inguinal Hernia", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hall, Nathan Christopher (d. 1889), "Scirrhus", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hallock, Wallace Eugene (d. 1918), "Scarlet Fever", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hartley, John Davis, "Phthisis Pulmonalis", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hartley, Sophia Meindermann (d. 1917), "Typhoid Fever" [Degree granted in 1875], 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hilton, Hattie Jean Tift, "Phthisis Pulmonalis", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hollister, Louis Eugene (d. 1917), "Conjunctivitis", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Holmes, George Wiley (d. 1910), "Origin and Distribution of Epidemics", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Hudson, Millard Fillmore (d. 1909), "Opium", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Huntley, Eusebia Neville (d. 1894), "Reproduction", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Huxley, Charles Ethelbert (d. 1908), "Scarlatina", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Jewell, Philo Milton (d. 1914), on pneumonia, 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Kay, Thomas Augustine (d. 1901), "The Medulla Oblongata", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Kellison, Charles (d. 1921), "Cerebro-Spinal Meningitis", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Kingsley, Josephine (d. 1907), "Infantile Convulsions", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Leffingwell, James Gibson (d. 1903), "Conjunctivitis", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - LeSeure, Oscar, "Apoplexy", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - Little, Mary Elizabeth (d. 1899), "The Primary Action of Medicines", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - MacChesney, Henrietta (Milsom) (d. 1907), "Pathology of Fever", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - McCorkle, John Alva (d. 1916), "Scarlatina", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - McGregor, John Owen, "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 45)
    - McGrew, Anna Julia (Lore), "The Excretory Function of the Liver", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - McIntyre, Robert (d. 1882), "Reproduction", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - McKnight, Virginia (Harley), "Diagnosis", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Martland, William Henry, "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Merriam, Laureston Alphonso (d. 1921), "Typho-Malarial Fever", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Miller, Thomas Owen (d. 1888), "Circulation of the Blood" [Degree granted in 1874], 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Millington, John (d. 1918), "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Moore, Philena, "Lung Diseases" [student paper], 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Morgan, Albert Lewis, "Intermittent Fever", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Munson, James Decker, "Epilepsy", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Murdock, Frank Hall (d. 1912), "Digestion", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Nicholson, Almon Wesley (d. 1907), "Nerve Centres (sic)-Phenomena of their External and Internal Relationships", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Nunan, Denis (d. 1902), "Inflammation", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Pease, Edward Everett, "Labor", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Perrin, Thomas Abram (d. 1913), "Fractures", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Phelps, Abel Mix (d. 1902), "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Phelps, Henry DeWitt Clinton, "Delirium Tremens", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Plews, Bradford Franklin (d. 1881), "Electro-Physiology", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Porter, John James (d. 1897), "Mercury", 1873 (Reel 46)
    - Porter, William Henry, "Typhoid Fever", 1873 (Reel 46)